So in this video we are going to
talk about a silent multibagger stock
which comes from Reliance group. There
is a difference between ICICI Lombard in the top.
So ICICI General Insurance, if we
look at it, we can see the problem
in the general insurance sector from India's side, the
market cap is around 6500. The
p.70 of the industry till the top 50, so the industry is
seen at cheap valuations. Their
love is displayed on a steady liquid 21,
Saturday zoom is seen,
correctly the stop is running around 1350,
if we look at it again, we see
around 1670 and the low is seen at 13 class
and correctly we are getting around talk per kg,
that
witnesses can be said, different jails in
more companies, oh descendants, oh it
goes with anger also and there is
no haunted place of our voters.
If this is its p.i chart, the
medium of password of the last five years is running around 58th yesterday's size
BNP, so the market
's  I did not participate separately in what he is saying. Let's
talk about the product. The company has become
almost free. The company has grown its profit by
38.0% in the last 15 years,
which is a good number.
Good different initiatives, different parities
can be read. There is a system about which if you talk about it, then
you are trading them one time from the book value. In
general, this is
seen in a lot of stocks. You will see this in this company for 5 minutes, so you
can ignore it. The promoter holding has
reduced by 3-4% in the last few quarters.
This is one reason. If you
look at it, it is a professionally managed group.
If you look at I Serum, HDFC Group,
you will see the promoter holding
decreasing because it is
professionally managed. If you look at it, the
basis of appointed crores is linked to it.
Talking about the loot tree, it
comes in insurance, but if you look at it, then no
operator is showing it, this is
not it. If you are a general insurance company, all these
come under its government company, till date never
reversed.  It should be done, the sector which comes out on a major,
it comes out only by
ICICI number, if there is any
interest in it, then it comes out from the only intersection,
Gan HD, there is no such thing
listed, then they can connect,
if the profit and loss of the company is seen in the last five years,
how has the sales been, then if we look at the profit and loss of the company in the last five years, then if we
see from 2015, 24 to three four crores
3037 520 62
26-1-14 65, it has been seen that the
sales have increased
more than four times, in the last years,
if we go towards the net profit, 585
507 202
8094,
land acquisition is seen,
two Gulhads are seen in the profit,
this 10 year powder is famous, it is a
very good turmeric powder around percent and
only in opposition, the district council is seen, if we
take it soon and run it like roti parantha, then the
promoter holding Sonth has taken the initiative
because earlier I had seen a lot  The
spokesperson has reduced the number of shares around the campus,
click on your button, so it is a good thing, whom is buying audio,
refer to the purchase of FD notification,
12% of the surrounding buildings,
now the border has doubled, the
increase in the area around the campus has been
one and a half inches, in fact, it has been done
around ten and a half to eleven percent and the
public shareholding has decreased, which was
around this year, so has your crop been done, so it is
quite good, one thing is
when is the public holding increasing, the
certificate of FD is increasing, which is quite good,
that pattern is also visible, let's talk about it, the
fundamentals are quite strong,
if the company is associated with this group, then
you can sit and invest in this,
after that see it is a futuristic business because the
insurance sector is doing quite well
and then we
can see Rahu on this, looking at the hatred towards Akshay companies in all the parameters,
then in one month one of the
best top 10 choices in six months from 2012 rib to
one year, the stock rate was tipped  10 on
St. Peters Square, if you look at the maximum, then
Kapoor, it's second properly
around 2017, less 2016 in the press and till now
you have got around 100% for the latest news, then the
watchman's money has doubled in 5,000 years,
which you are getting a lot of
details, but digital can clearly say,
now let's talk about stop this prayer, you should buy
if you see the stock rate was
around 670 and lessons are being seen on agriculture,
which is giving first priority,
you can buy it, that is CMP,
it is quite attractive, even before this, a couple of times by
taking stock support, the boss has
ordered a bus, now we see
and the juice is around honeycombs, if
that is also clear, let's see, then
basically RSS leftover soldier has gone
around extremism, if
you are getting the introduction of fundamentally strong company class
due to the image of the posted, then it is
quite good for children,
now let's talk about at what price you
can think about buying  If you have
passed the balance and got your medical done in Karachi, then around a few hours of
leave, then you can comfortably
think about talking to him directly. The
world is in a trap of mental strength, it cannot be predicted much.
That's all for today's video.
To see such interesting videos, you
can mute subscribe, you can like it,
go to Tempchar and get updates on coffee.
Now, keep posting it in this, everyone will get
training, till then
bye-bye.